





Artificial Intelligence Specialist

ABOUT

Who I am:

I'm Arsenii, an AI specialist. I graduated with the Computer Science and NLP degree from Ludwig Maximilian University in Munich. I like to research, look for creative solutions, and tinker on difficult problems using AI.

Where I am currently at:

Currently, I work as AI Developer at PwC. There, I engineer AI solutions for complex business requirements.

What is my goal:

To become a go-to expert in AI, travel the world and consult companies on how to improve their businesses with AI. I would like to be invited to a project that will have a great impact on our society.



PROJECTS

2023/12 Abstract Segmentation for Medical Texts

Repo

Segmentation of medical research abstracts into named paragraphs. Could achieve a test accuracy of 80% and a test-weighted mean F1 score of almost 60%.

TensorFlow / Data Preprocessing / Multi-modality

2024/01 Knowledge Graph Embeddings

Reno

Embedding synthetic knowledge graphs via non-neural algorithms like TransE, DistMult, ComplEx using Ampli-

graph API.

GenAI Data / Knowledge Graphs / Embeddings

2024/06 Spatial Reasoning for LLMs

Rep

Exploring Spatial Reasoning Abilities of LLMs. I fine-tuned my own LLM and navigated 2D and 3D spaces with it. LLM Benchmarking / Fine-tuning / Research

EXPERIENCE

2024/9 - Present

Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics Developer

PwC

- End-to-end integration of multiple GenAI, GenOps and RAG tools.
- Leader of AI technologies club with over 50 active members.
- · Engineering cloud and on-prem solutions.

2022/2 – 2024/9 Artificial Intelligence Engineer

Ehoss

- On-prem computer vision, predictive analytics.
- Testing VLMs, such as Florence 2 for geospatial data analytics in GCP.
- · Representing startup's AI solutions on exhibitions abroad.

2022/7 – 2024/3 **Software Developer**

Materna

- ServiceNow large-scale application development.
- Working across the whole stack to deliver robust and scalable solutions.
- Design, implementation and testing of over 20 complex workflows.

- Teaching programming for a total of 200 hours.
- · Supervising students' projects and refining them.
- Modernizing 100+ pages of learning materials.

EDUCATION

2021/11 – 2024/9 Bachelor of Science (BSc) in Computer Science and NLP

LMU Munich

LMU is one of the most prestigious universities in Germany. My favorite lecture was "Introduction into NLP". Bachelor's Thesis: "Spatial Reasoning in LLMs",

2020/11 – 2021/9 Bachelor of Science (BSc) in Physics

THM

TUM is the best technical university in Germany. I started studying Physics and then after a year decided to switch to Computer Science at LMU.

CERTIFICATES

2024/3 TensorFlow Developer

Google

You can find me among global certified TensorFlow developers here.

2024/5 Introduction to AI and Machine Learning on Google Cloud

Google

Learned how to build models in the Cloud. Specifically: Vertex AI, BigQury and AutoML.

LANGUAGES

- English (C1)
- German (C1)
- Slovak (C1)
- Ukrainian (C1)
- Russian (C1)
- French (A2)

OTHER

• Driver license - AM, B and B1 - 3 years of active experience

STILL HAVE QUESTIONS?

Ask my personal chatbot.